pcwin.com 2002-02-06

# PCWin Resource Center - Privacy Statement

  | 

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

iiSi has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for PCWin Resource Center.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your download cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly.

This site contains links to other sites. **PCWin Resource Center** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We do not and will not sell our mailing list or access to our mailing list nor will we divulge any personal information about any of our visitors with anyone, anything or organization.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

Sometimes we use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

## Public Forums

This site makes forums or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use firewalls and other state of the art tools to protect our network and only one person, the webmaster (Randy Burgess) has access to all collected information.

## Children's Guidelines

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@pcwin.com](mailto:webmaster@pcwin.com?Subject=Privacy%20Statement)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [webmaster@pcwin.com](mailto:webmaster@pcwin.com?Subject=Privacy%20Statement)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contactRandy Burgess Internet Information Solutions, Inc. PO Box 338 Travelers Rest, SC 29690 [randy@pcwin.com](mailto:randy@pcwin.com)

* * *

This website dedicated to Ann H. Burgess
  | 

## PRIVACY STATEMENT

iiSi has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for PCWin Resource Center.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your download cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly.

This site contains links to other sites. **PCWin Resource Center** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We do not and will not sell our mailing list or access to our mailing list nor will we divulge any personal information about any of our visitors with anyone, anything or organization.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

Sometimes we use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

## Public Forums

This site makes forums or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use firewalls and other state of the art tools to protect our network and only one person, the webmaster (Randy Burgess) has access to all collected information.

## Children's Guidelines

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@pcwin.com](mailto:webmaster@pcwin.com?Subject=Privacy%20Statement)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [webmaster@pcwin.com](mailto:webmaster@pcwin.com?Subject=Privacy%20Statement)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contactRandy Burgess Internet Information Solutions, Inc. PO Box 338 Travelers Rest, SC 29690 [randy@pcwin.com](mailto:randy@pcwin.com)

* * *

This website dedicated to Ann H. Burgess
